[
  {
    "question": "What is an EBS Snapshot?",
    "options": [
      "An operation system on an EC2 instance",
      "A backup of your EBS volume at a point in time",
      "The amount of CPU and RAM of an EC2 instance",
      "A screenshot of your EC2 instance"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an EBS Volume tied to?",
    "options": [
      "A Region",
      "A Data center",
      "An Edge Location",
      "An Availability Zone"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement is CORRECT regarding EBS?",
    "options": [
      "An EBS can be mounted to multiple instances at a time",
      "An EBS can be used in a regional scale",
      "You can control the EBS behavior when an EC2 instance is terminated",
      "You cannot copy snapshots across Regions"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "EBS Volumes CANNOT be attached to multiple EC2 instances at a time.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "An EBS Volume is a network drive you can attach to your instances while they run, so your instances' data persist even after their termination.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "An EBS is limited to an AZ, there is no way to move the volume across AZs.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) is an object storage suitable for the storage of flat files like Microsoft Word documents, photos, etc.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Amazon S3 replicates all objects",
    "options": [
      "on multiple volumes within an Availability Zone",
      "in multiple Availability Zones within the same Region",
      "across multiple Regions for higher durability",
      "on multiple S3 buckets"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following can be used as a storage class for an S3 object lifecycle policy? (Choose three)",
    "options": [
      "S3-Standard Access",
      "AWS Storage Gateway",
      "S3-Infrequent Access",
      "Simple Storage Service Glacier",
      "S3- Reduced Redundancy Storage",
      "Amazon Dynamo DB"
    ],
    "correctIndex": [
      0,
      2,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The name of an S3 bucket must be unique",
    "options": [
      "worldwide across all AWS accounts",
      "within a Region",
      "across all your AWS accounts",
      "within your AWS account"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "You can use Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) to:",
    "options": [
      "provide simple, scalable, elastic file storage for use only within AWS.",
      "implement storage for Amazon EC2 instances that multiple virtual machines can access at the same time.",
      "host a robust CDN to deliver entire web sites with dynamic, static, and streaming content.",
      "generate user-specific content."
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) is recommended when data (Choose two)",
    "options": [
      "requires object-level storage",
      "must be quickly accessible, requiring long-term persistence",
      "requires an encryption solution",
      "needs to be stored in a different Availability Zone than the one the EC2 instance is in"
    ],
    "correctIndex": [
      1,
      2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? By default, all data stored in Amazon S3 is viewable by the public.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Regarding Amazon S3 Glacier, what is a Vault?",
    "options": [
      "The rules that determine who may (or may not) access archives",
      "An object (photos, videos, files, or documents)",
      "A container for storing archives",
      "A policy that identifies who can access content stored in Glacier"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? When you create a bucket in Amazon S3, it is associated with a specific AWS Region.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are features of Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)? (Choose two)",
    "options": [
      "Amazon EBS volumes can be encrypted transparently to workloads on the attached instance.",
      "Data on an Amazon EBS volume is lost when the attached instance is stopped.",
      "Amazon EBS data is automatically backed up to tape.",
      "Data stored on Amazon EBS is automatically replicated within an Availability Zone."
    ],
    "correctIndex": [
      0,
      3
    ]
  }
]